戒酒匿名會
戒酒十二步
美國國會  歸檔提案
HR684號提案
安德沃
馬修
馬修副總統
Vice President Matthews.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
安德沃
沃麥克
吉普森
馬修
- 副總統先生  - 法蘭
-Mr. Vice President.  -Frank.
長官，你得站在記號上
Sir, I'm gonna need you  to stand on your mark.
這裏就好
I'm fine right here.
還有兩分鐘
Two minutes, people.
他們把我從車裏拖出來  雙腿骨折，頭骨破裂
So they pull me from the car,  both legs broken, fractured skull,
肺部穿孔
punctured lung.
我的心臟停止跳動
My heart stops.
整整兩分鐘
Two full minutes.
他們替我做心肺復甦術  沒反應
They're pumping my chest. Nothing.
用電擊器
They grab the defibrillators.
沒反應
Nothing.
第三次，我的心臟才開始跳動
Third time, the pistons start firin'.
醫生說我能活下來  簡直是奇蹟
Doctors tell me it's a miracle I'm alive.
但神真的把我點醒了
But seriously, you talk about  a wake-up call from God.
死而復生不會發生第二次
You don't get to  come back from the dead twice.
美國總統
The President of the United States.
早安
Good morning.
我今天簽署的  教育改革與成就法案
The Education Reform and Achievement Act  that I sign into law today
會影響全美每位孩童和父母
will affect every child and parent  in the United States,
會在未來十年  提高勞動人口教育素質
will ensure a better educated workforce  for decades to come,
也會鞏固美國  卓越知識強國的地位
and will reinforce America's pre-eminence  as an intellectual superpower.
我想特別感謝一個人
And I'd like to thank one man in particular,
他從未忘記更重要的使命
who never lost sight of the larger mission,
他從一開始  就為此提案衝鋒陷陣
who spearheaded this bill  from the beginning.
那就是議員法蘭安德沃
And that's Congressman Frank Underwood.
葛瑞沃克
請來賓們到東廂享用茶點
Invited guests, please join us  in the East Room for refreshments.
媒體朋友請至簡報室  我們將馬上進行記者會
Media, we will convene immediately  in the Briefing Room for our conference.
琳達，非常感謝你的協助  讓我們通過提案
Linda, thank you so much for all the help  you gave us in getting this bill passed.
要謝謝你才對，法蘭  這是你的傑作
No, thank you, Frank.  This was your baby from the beginning.
感謝你這次堅守立場，法蘭
I appreciate you  standing your ground on this one, Frank.
我也算聰明  即時承認了錯誤
I'm smart enough to admit when I was wrong.
我剛跟法蘭說  我們應該設周會
I was just telling Frank  we should set up a weekly,
讓他跟我們匯報眾議院的情況
so he can keep us up-to-date  on what's going on in the House.
這主意很棒
That sounds like a great idea.
- 恭喜，長官  - 葛瑞…
-Congratulations, sir.  -Garrett...
能不能跟你談一下
I was wondering  if we could talk for a few minutes.
幾周前我跟你提過的那件事
That thing I mentioned  a couple of weeks ago,
就業抵稅優惠…
about the jobs tax credit...
我考慮過了，吉姆  這主意不錯
I've been giving it a lot of thought, Jim,  and I think it's a good idea,
但如果你不介意  我想先看一下我的筆記
but I'd like to look over my notes first,  ifyou don't mind,
好跟你討論一些實質內容
so I can talk about it intelligently with you.
長官，首相在線上
Sir, you have your call  with the Prime Minister.
- 大忙人  - 沒錯
-Busy man.  -Yes, he is.
法蘭，聽說你要統籌  我家鄉那州的補選
Frank, I hear that you are heading up  the special election in my home state.
彼得魯索
Peter Russo.
在正式宣佈之前  我們不想讓太多人知道
We're trying to keep that under the radar  until he officially announces.
事實上，在確定之前  我們不會進辦公室
In fact, we're not even working  out of my office until that happens.
- 那你們在哪準備？  - 我家地下室
-Where are you working from?  -The basement of my house.
你知道為什麼麼民主黨全委會  沒有問我的意見嗎？
Any reason why the DNC  didn't ask my advice on the candidate?
我以為他們或琳達問過你了
Well, I thought they passed it by you,  or that Linda did.
沒人跟我說過
Nobody did.
太過分了
Well, that is unacceptable.
- 我很懷疑魯索的能力  - 他缺乏經驗？
-And I have major doubts about Russo.  -His inexperience?
對，他是在城市長大  不知道能不能跟鄉村選名產生共鳴
Yes. And he's urban-based.  I don't know if he'll connect with rural voters.
老實說，這也是我的擔心之一
Look, frankly that's one of  my concerns as well.
我們在想辦法
We're working on that.
但如果你能支持他  幫他站台
But if you were to come out  and stump with him,
那就能說服很多…
that would go a long way to convince...
法蘭，我不能幫我不相信的人站台
Frank, I can't stump  for somebody I don't believe in.
現在還早，我希望你能放寬心胸
It's early days yet.  I'd ask you to keep an open mind.
如果你希望跟他見面就告訴我
And let me know if you want me  to set up a meeting between the two of you.
長官，因為你的支持  對他會是非常大的幫助
Because, sir, an endorsement from you  would be a big coup for him.
- 見到你真好，副總統先生  - 法蘭
-It's good to see you, Mr. Vice President.  -Frank.
安德沃議員
Congressman Underwood.
邦斯小姐，我記得  你不想報導白宮新聞
Ms. Barnes. I was under the impression  you didn't want to cover the White House.
- 《頭條報導》昨天剛拿到通行證  - 我知道
-Slugline just got access yesterday.  -I know.
我離開《先軀報》  因為不想報導白宮新聞
I left The Herald because I didn't want  to cover the White House,
結果我又被派來了
and now here I am.
通行證和腳鐐不一樣
Access isn't the same as a ball and chain.
只有在簽署提案時才能見面？
Am I only gonna see you  at bill signings now?
我已經三周沒聽到你的消息
I haven't heard from you in three weeks.
我不喜歡不安全感
Insecurity bores me.
屈尊俯就也是
I feel the same way about condescension.
你家，今晚  我到之前會傳簡訊給你
Your place. This evening.  And I'll text when I'm about to arrive.
如果我在忙呢？
What if I'm busy?
你只是怕我又放你鴿子
You're just afraid  I'm gonna stand you up again.
我只想確定我不會白等
I just want to make sure it's worth my while.
不會讓你白等的  這應該能補償上一次
It'll be worth your while.  This'll make up for last time.
歷史的見證  從總統手裏交到你手裏
It's a piece of history.  From the President's hand to yours.
你相信他們在會議室裏說的  至高無上權力嗎？
You believe in all that higher power stuff  they talk about in the room?
我相信有些事情  是我們無法控制的
I believe there are things beyond our control.
我不知道誰或什麼在控制
Who or what's controlling them,  that I don't know.
我不相信神  也不相信天堂地獄這些東西
I don't believe in God.  Heaven. Hell. None of it.
- 在天主教學校裏太久了？  - 也許吧
-Too much Catholic school?  -Maybe.
我不是說你一定要相信神  或是類似的東西，彼得
I'm not saying you have to believe in God,  Peter, or anything for that matter.
但你不該否定任何事情
But you shouldn't rule anything out.
我得走了
I should go.
競選經費出
It's on the campaign.
道格史坦普
華府國會大樓
我需要更多錢
這次不要在我嘴裏  202- 148- 0215
交叉數據顯示81%的選民
Our cross tabs show 81% of likely voters
願意考慮在戒酒的酒癮患者
are willing to consider  a recovering alcoholic.
如果是古柯堿
Now, those numbers dip a little
數字會下降，但不是很多
when you introduce cocaine,  but not by much.
蘭迪？
Randy?
有風險，但肯定會造成話題
It's a risk, but it'll make waves.
有全面的免費宣傳效果  主題是救贖
Free coverage across the board.  The narrative has to be redemption,
鳳凰從灰燼中重生
a phoenix from the ashes.
別強調灰燼
Well, let's not focus on the ashes.
別讓大家覺得彼得是個災難
We don't want people to think  Peter was a disaster.
不會  我們會著重在正面的事物
No, no. We focus on the positive.
「重新出發」和「除去污點」  兩者評價都不錯
A "fresh start" and a "clean start"  both did well in focus groups.
「除去污點」  會讓人有不好的聯想
"Clean start" sounds too  much like "clean slate."
- 我喜歡「重新出發」  - 我也是
-I like "fresh start."  -Yeah, I do too.
募款方面呢？
How we doing on the fundraising?
酒癮的事  會阻礙一些州內的捐款
The alcoholic thing will turn off  some of the in-state donors,
但這不是大選
but it's an off-year election.
可以找紐約和加州的贊助人
We can hit up the usual suspects  in New York and California.
華特，我們有多脆弱？
Walter, how vulnerable are we?
這問題我還回答不了
I'm not prepared to answer that question.
彼得還沒跟我進行過懺悔儀式
Peter and I have yet to perform  the holy sacrament of confession.
我們也要解決造船廠關閉的事
We still need to address  the shipyard closing, too.
克萊兒在幫忙了
Claire's helping us with that.
我們在推動  德拉瓦河分水嶺法案
We are pushing a bill  called the Delaware River Watershed Act
應該能為彼得的選區  在三年內帶來大約
and I think it's going to bring  about 5,000 jobs into Peter's districts
五千個就業機會
over the next three years.
草案已經完成了
We have a draft of the bill completed.
彼得正在連絡其他贊助人
Peter's in the process  of securing co-sponsors.
你連絡過誰了？
And who have you called, by the way?
我發了幾封電子郵件  但大部分都想先看過提案
I have some emails out,  but most of them wanna see a bill first.
你和造船廠員工見面了嗎？
Have you set up a meeting  with the shipbuilders yet?
他們不會支持
I don't think they're gonna back me.
這個提案  就是為了他們立的，彼得
That's the entire point of the bill, Peter.
如果我去跟他們說
Well, if I go to them and I say,
「你們之中有些人  或許會再有工作機會
"Hey, some of you  maybe will get your jobs back,
「不是明天，而是三年後
"not tomorrow, but three years from now,
「反正大部分的人  也不會有工作…」
"and most of you  won't be getting your jobs back anyway..."
好了，先找更多贊助人再說
All right, let's put a pin in this  until we get more sponsors.
我得回辦公室了  晚點再討論
I have to go to the office.  I'll catch you all later.
現在來談在地計劃
Okay, let's move on to our field plan.
我想逐一討論每個地區…
I want to go through  the regions one by one...
法蘭斯
Francis.
那提案花了我們六周
We spent six weeks on that bill.
沒問題，他會醒過來的
It'll be fine. He'll come around.
今晚見？
I'll see you later tonight?
我有約了
I have an appointment.
所以得等到早上了
So I won't see you until morning.
我會在你起床前回來的
I'll be back before you get up.
謝謝你今天撥出時間，長官
I appreciate your taking the time today, sir.
你有收到經濟研究小組的  抵稅優惠備忘錄嗎？
Did you get that tax credit memo  the economic research team put together?
你不是要來問我這件事
You didn't ask me here to talk about memos.
我聽得出來閒聊，琳達
I know small talk when I hear it, Linda.
總統先生希望  你不要插手賓州的事
The President has asked  that you take a step back from Pennsylvania.
你最近回去了很多次  和國會議員見面…
You've been taking a lot of trips there,  meeting with legislators...
那是我的家鄉  現在有就業危機
It's my home state. There's a jobs crisis.
我們不能有偏袒
We can't afford to play favorites.
重點是50個州  一個解決方案
The message is 50 states, one solution.
而不是反過來
Not one state, 50 solutions.
我從沒指望參與  每一項政策和決定
I never expected to be involved  in every policy or decision,
但我完全被架空了
but I have been completely  cut out of everything.
我們重視你的付出，副總統先生  但現在不能…
We value your input, Mr. Vice President,  but right now, we can't...
別客套了，琳達
Don't condescend, Linda.
甚至沒人問過我  我的繼任者應該是誰
No one even asked me  who I thought should fill my seat.
為什麼是法蘭安德沃主導  而不是我？
Why is Frank Underwood  leading the charge on that, not me?
這是民主黨全委會的事情
That is a DNC issue.
我們已經置身事外  你也應該這樣
We are staying out of it and so should you.
所以我只能去剪綵  和參加葬禮？
And so I'm supposed to just cut ribbons  and go to funerals?
你明白這個職位的性質
You know what you signed up for.
謝謝你，副總統先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
我沒拿到我的筆
I didn't get my pen.
- 你的筆？  - 簽署提案的那支筆
-Your pen?  -From the bill signing.
我們會想辦法
We'll see what we can do about that.
- 我能看到你的保鏢  - 米契？
-I can see your security guy.  -Meechum?
他蠻帥的
He's cute.
他不會對你有意思的
He'd never go for you.
為什麼？
Why not?
你太嚇人了
You're too intimidating.
他有槍
He's the one with the gun.
你有議員
But you're the one with the Congressman.
我們之後再談
We'll talk after.
我們先談
We'll talk before.
彼得魯索
Peter Russo.
賓州第一選區，他要競選州長
Pennsylvania's first district.  He's gonna run for Governor,
接替馬修的位子  這是獨家新聞
fill Matthews' seat. It's an exclusive profile.
一個沒沒無聞的人
With someone no one's ever heard of.
切入角度呢？
What's the angle?
酒精、毒品
Alcohol, drugs.
從小是街頭混混
He's a kid from the streets.
我要報導在他宣佈之後  第一時間發表
I want the profile to come out  as soon as he announces,
要友善一點
and I'd like it to be kind.
我不寫拍馬屁的文章
I don't write puff pieces.
那就讓別人寫
Then get someone else to write it.
我以為你有帶東西給我
I thought you had something for me.
這樣別人很容易  把我和你聯想在一起
It's too easy for people  to link me as your source.
太危險了
It's dangerous.
把頭條報導讓給別人  對我沒好處
I don't benefit from handing out  headlines to other people.
慷慨就是力量，喬伊
Generosity is its own form of power, Zoe.
第六步
Step six.
把另一邊摺到…
Take the opposite edge and fold it into a...
第七步
Step seven.
翻轉過來，把兩邊往中間摺
Turn the model over and fold both  edges to the center of the model.
你晚上都戴墨鏡？
You always wear sunglasses at night?
你怎麼找到我的？
How did you find me?
我想你一定是公務員  就上網搜尋，找到你的照片
I figured you had to be in government.  I kept googling till I found your picture.
你這樣做沒有用
This won't work, what you're doing.
那是一次交易  你不能一直索求無度
That was a one-time deal.  You don't get to keep coming back for more.
我會去報警
I'll go to the police.
他們會當面嘲笑你  看看你自己
They'll laugh in your face. Look at you.
如果警察不聽  我就會打給電視台
If the police won't listen to me,  I'll call TV stations.
名字我都知道…
I know the names...
道格史坦普、彼得魯索  法蘭安德沃
Douglas Stamper, Peter Russo,  Frank Underwood.
你不會想走這條不歸路的
You are walking down a road  you do not want to walk down.
拜託，我不會打給任何人
Please, I won't call anyone.
但我需要你的幫助
But I need your help.
我沒有地方去  沒有可以打電話求助的人
I don't have anywhere to go.  I don't have anyone I can call.
我必須做事，我不想再做了
I've had to do things.  And I don't want to do it anymore.
我只有這麼多
That's all I've got right now.
找個地方住，再告訴我地點
Find a place to stay  and let me know where you are.
我會想辦法
I'll figure something out.
你餓了嗎？
You hungry?
你叫什麼名字？
What's your name?
藍寶石
Sapphire.
我是問你的真名
No. What's your name?
瑞秋
Rachel.
- 你的前妻有不雅的事嗎？  - 什麼意思？
-Your ex-wife. Anything uncouth?  -How do you mean?
- 性虐待、雜交派對、喝尿？  - 絕對沒有
-Bondage, orgies, water sports?  -No. Definitely not.
- 毒品呢？  - 她不喜歡
-Narcotics?  -She wasn't into that.
連大麻都沒有？
Not even a little ganga?
好吧，少之又少
Okay, once in a blue moon.
- 和孩子一起做過嗎？  - 天啊，沒有！
-Ever with your children?  -God, no!
在他們面前？
Ever in front of them?
我不是模範爸爸  但我絕不會這樣做
Look, I'm not the world's best dad,  but I would never do that.
好，接著說買春的事
Fine. Let's move on to prostitution.
這還要搞多久？
How long is this gonna take?
直到我完全瞭解你
Until there's nothing I don't know about you.
我都寫下來了
I wrote all this down.
我做這行很久了，議員
I've been doing this  a long time, Congressman.
等我問完所有的事就會停止
I know when I've scraped  all the shit off the shoe.
買春
Prostitution.
離婚之後  我去泰國旅行大概兩周
After my divorce, I took a trip to Thailand.  It was about two weeks.
幾個女人？
How many women?
10、15個
Ten. Fifteen.
我…不知道，印象有點模糊
I... I don't know. It was a bit of a blur.
- 有毒品嗎？  - 有
-There were drugs?  -Yes.
鴉片、安非他命、海洛因
Opium, speed, some smack.
- 吸的還是注射的？  - 都有
-Powder or needles?  -Both.
這些女人認識你嗎？
Would any of these women  know who you are?
不會，她們不會說英文  我沒提過我是議員
No. None of them spoke English.  And I never mentioned I was a congressman.
你在美國注射過海洛因嗎？
Have you mainlined heroin  back here in the States?
- 只有一次  - 手臂上疤痕嗎？
-Just once.  -Any scars on your arm?
沒有，我主要是吸古柯堿
No. I was mainly into cocaine.
在華府買春有多頻繁？
What about prostitutes here in D.C.?  How often?
- 我是有點亂搞  - 說細節
-I fucked around a bit, okay?  -Details, please.
聽這種事會讓你興奮嗎？
Do you get off on this or something?
醫生抓住你的睪丸  叫你咳嗽時
Does a doctor enjoy it  when he cups your balls
你覺得他享受嗎？
and asks you to cough?
想知道我高潮幾次？
You wanna know how many times I came?
我根本不關心你會不會贏
I honestly don't care whether you win.
但如果你關心，就跟我合作
But if you do, work with me.
你在華府買春有多頻繁？
How often did you solicit prostitutes in D.C.?
兩、三個月一次，或多或少
Once every two or three months.  Sometimes more frequently, sometimes less.
其中有未成年的嗎？
Do you have reason to believe  any of them were underage?
天啊！沒有  她們大多是高級妓女
Jesus! No. Look, they were mostly high-end.
- 不代表她們滿18歲  - 我要休息！
-That doesn't mean they were 18.  -I need a fucking break!
怎麼了？
What's going on?
他太嫩了，法蘭
He's an amateur, Frank.
如果我不用一小時  就能把他惹毛
If I can get under his skin  in less than an hour,
他在媒體前會撐得住嗎？
how do you think  he'll hold up under the press?
根本是大屠殺
It'll be a turkey shoot.
好吧，我去跟他談
All right. I'll speak to him.
法蘭，沒用的  我會被批判到死
Frank, it's just, it's not gonna work.  I'm gonna get crucified.
不會有事的  我們有一流團隊支持你
You'll be fine.  We've got a crack team behind you.
不管團隊有多優秀  是我過去的事，拜託
It doesn't matter how good the team is.  With my past? Come on.
我從一開始  就告訴你這個計劃
From the very beginning,  I said this was the plan.
- 你也同意  - 我沒想清楚
-You agreed to it.  -I didn't think it through.
我們必須面對問題  不然共和黨會把你批判到死
We have to tackle this head-on,  or the GOP will crucify you.
要把他們的彈藥偷過來
We have to steal their ammunition from them.
誠實是你最好的攻防
Honesty is your best defense and offense.
我才是要站在攝影機前  說那些話的人
I'm the one that has to get in front of  these cameras and say this shit.
不是他們，是我
They don't have to say it. I do.
- 彼得…  - 我真的想做州長
-Peter...  -I wanna be governor. I do.
但我做不到
But not this way. I just can't do it.
如果你現在沒有動搖  那就有問題了
If you weren't unsure now,  there'd be something wrong with you.
早在我預料中
I expected this.
我們要你做的事情是不容易
Not easy, what we're asking you to do.
猶豫是正常的
It's okay to vacillate a little.
我不想拖後腿
I'm not trying to throw  a wrench in the works.
我知道，這樣吧
I know you're not. I'll tell you what.
你今天先回去休息  明天回辦公室
You take the rest of the day off.  You go back to your office,
去做你該做的事情
you catch up  with whatever you have to catch up on,
好好睡一覺，明天去戒酒會
you get a good night's sleep,  you go to a meeting tomorrow,
再回來這裏  我們把事情談清楚
and then you come here  and we'll talk the whole thing through.
這樣可以吧？
Can you give me at least that?
- 好，法蘭  - 很好
-Yeah. Okay, Frank.  -Good.
那些小藝術品是什麼意思？
What's going on  with all the little sculptures?
我在餐桌上發現一朵花
I found a flower on the dining room table
幾天前還在床頭櫃發現一隻鳥
and a bird on the nightstand a few days ago.
是天鵝
It's a swan.
- 你摺的？  - 對
-You made them?  -Yes.
新嗜好？
A new hobby?
不是
No.
只是有興趣
It's an interest.
我還注意到一件事  可以說嗎？
May I bring up something else I've noticed?
什麼事？
What's that?
你…
You...
站在冰箱前
Standing in front of the refrigerator.
你有事還沒告訴我嗎？
Is there a reason  you haven't talked to me about it?
沒有必要說
I haven't felt the need to.
很糟嗎？
Is it bad?
不太好
It's not pleasant.
但也不至於糟
But, no, it's not bad.
我能做什麼嗎？
What can I do?
不用
Nothing.
有需要我會說
If there were something, I'd ask.
- 我打給你很奇怪嗎？  - 非常奇怪
-Did you think it was weird that I called you?  -Totally weird.
不過我也準備找你
Except for the fact  that I was planning on calling you.
真的嗎？為什麼？
Really? Why?
在《先軀報》的時候  我實在太刻薄了
I was a real grade-A bitch  to you at The Herald,
我在白宮看到你的時候  差點就跟你道歉
and I almost apologized  when I saw you at the White House,
但我沒勇氣
but I chickened out.
我現在醉了，對不起
So, anyway, I am drunk enough,  and I am sorry.
你為什麼會打給我？
Why did you call me?
我只是想知道報社的近況
I was just wondering how things were going  at the old stomping ground.
- 你的飲料  - 謝謝
-Here you go.  -Thank you.
湯姆走了以後  一切都不一樣了
It's just not the same since Tom left.
我不怪你做的那些事
And I don't blame you  for doing what you did.
但這個新主管？
But this new guy?
六年《線上娛樂週刊》經驗  不夠格當報社主編
Six years running EW Online  does not a managing editor make.
你想來我們這裏嗎？
Would you ever want to come work with us?
這絕對是大新聞
I mean, it'd be a huge fucking deal.
《先軀報》的首席政治記者  跳槽到《頭條報導》？
Chief Political Correspondent  of The Herald moves to Slugline?
是卡莉希斯叫你來的嗎？
Did Carly Heath put you up to this?
不是，但如果你想  我可以去找她談
No. Not at all.  But if you want, I could talk to her.
你覺得她會同意嗎？
You think she would go for it?
我真的不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
她有這種反體制的強勢態度
She's got this sort of  anti-establishment "fuck you" attitude.
她覺得傳統新聞很無聊
Conventional news bores her.
但如果你有勇氣…
But if you had something gritty to show...
如果你要，我有條新聞
I've got a story if you want it.
保證獨家
It's pretty fucking great.
你要把獨家拱手讓人？
You would give away a story?
如果你沒興趣…
If you're not interested...
我有興趣
No, I'm interested.
如果我看起來像宿醉  那是因為我真的宿醉
If I seem a little hung-over, it is because I am.
其實是很嚴重的宿醉
A lot hung-over, actually.
天啊，差點撐過兩個月了
God, I almost had a couple of months,
結果昨晚我…
and then last night, l...
我記不清楚了，所以…
Well, I don't remember much, so...
但我還是來了
But anyway, here I am.
記得要回來
Keep coming back.
只要努力就會成功
It works if you work it.
謝謝你的分享，黛安
Thank you for sharing, Diane.
我叫道格，我是酒癮患者
I'm Doug, and I'm an alcoholic.
你好，道格
Hi, Doug.
我的工作是計數
One of the things I do for a living is count.
我數選票
I count votes.
贊成、反對、中立、廢票
Yeas, nays, neutrals, abstaining.
我很在行
And I'm good at it.
但我最重要的計數  竟和工作無關
But the most important count I do  has nothing to do with work.
就是從1999年4月4日  至今的天數
It's the number of days since April 4, 1999.
到今早為止，已經5185天了
As of this morning, that's 5,185.
數字越大，我的恐懼就越大
The bigger that number gets,  the more it frightens me,
因為我知道，只要一杯酒  一切就會歸零
because I know all it takes is one drink  to go back to zero.
大部分的人都把恐懼視為弱點
Most people see fear as a weakness.
的確是
It can be.
有時候我的工作  就是要讓別人感到恐懼
Sometimes for my job,  I have to put fear in other people.
我知道這樣不對
I know that's not right.
但如果我要像  第四步要求的那樣誠實
But if I'm honest,  like the fourth step asks us to be,
我就必須殘忍
I have to be ruthless,
因為失敗不是選項之一
because failure is not an option.
這同樣適用我的戒酒
The same goes for my sobriety.
我必須對自己殘忍
I have to be ruthless with myself.
我必須利用我的恐懼
I have to use my fear.
恐懼讓我變得更堅強
It makes me stronger.
我和在座各位一樣  無法控制自己是誰
Like everyone in this room,  I can't control who I am.
但我可以控制那個零
But I can control the zero.
去他媽的零
Fuck the zero.
謝謝你的分享  只要努力就會成功
Thanks for sharing. It works if you work it.
接下來誰要分享？
Who would like to share next?
- 他去戒酒會了嗎？  - 去了
-Was he at the meeting?  -He was.
結束後我想找他
I tried to find him afterwards,
但是他已經離開了
but he was gone  before I could catch up with him.
- 他有說什麼嗎？  - 沒有
-Did he say anything?  -No.
他從來不分享  看起來心事重重
He never shares. He looked preoccupied.
- 他今天會來我家嗎？  - 不知道
-You think he'll show up at the house today?  -I have no idea.
他不接我電話
He's not answering my calls.
也不接我的  還有什麼我需要知道的嗎？
Mine neither. Anything else I need to know?
我不喜歡沉默的聲音
I hear silence. I don't like that sound.
出了點事，我在處理
Something came up. I'm handling it.
- 嚴重嗎？  - 嚴重，但是可以解決
-Something serious?  -Serious but solvable.
- 我想知道更多嗎？  - 應該不想，沒問題的
-Do I wanna know more?  -I don't think you do. We'll be okay.
我可能得找南茜，希望不會
I might have to involve Nancy.  I'm hoping I won't have to.
但如果非找她不可  我不會讓她知道細節
But if I do, she'll have no knowledge  of anything damaging.
好，仔細判斷
All right. Use your best judgment.
當然，議員
Of course, sir.
我得掛了
I've gotta go.
葛蘭格小姐？
Miss Gallagher?
可以跟議員說句話嗎？
Can the Congressman have a moment?
事情…很複雜
Things are... They're complicated.
我知道，但他真的需要你
I realize that, but he truly needs you.
我不知道能怎麼說
I don't know what I could say to him.
只要你出現  對他就很有幫助了
I think just showing up  would do him a world of good.
今天很難  發言人行程很滿…
Today is tough.  The Speaker has a full schedule...
我跟鮑伯說了  他說你今天可以請假
Look, I already spoke to Bob,  and he said he'd be fine
沒問題
ifyou took the rest of the day off.
事實上，他說  如果你想請六個月假
In fact, he said it'd be fine  ifyou wanted to take
- 也沒關係  - 什麼？
-the next six months off.  -What?
我要你來當競選部副主委
I want you to be deputy campaign manager.
跟著奈許亞倫做事
You work under Nash Aarons.
我當彼得的助手很多年了  如果你想要我…
No. I spent years being Peter's crutch.  If you just want me there...
我們當然想要你來幫忙  但不是助手
Well, of course we want you there to help,  but not as a crutch.
彼得很有才華，有無限可能
Peter is a talented young man  with a lot of potential.
他自己知道
He knows this,
但他得聽別人說
but he needs to hear it  from someone other than me.
一個他真正關心的人
Someone he truly cares about.
對不起  我一下子接受不了這麼多
I'm sorry. This is just a lot right now.
你不必現在做決定
Well, you don't have to make a decision now,
至少去跟彼得聊聊
but at least talk to Peter.
不會有什麼壞處吧？
I mean, there's no harm in that,  now, is there?
一萬
10 grand.
從你的競選資金裏出
We divert it from your campaign accounts.
- 會標明是…  - 等等
-We itemize it so it looks like...  -Wait.
你們要我買單？
You want me to pay for this?
用法蘭的競選連任資金
Use Frank's re-election fund.
局長，你大部分的募款
Commissioner, the majority of  the money that you've raised
都來自我們為你找來的人
has come from people we've sent your way.
那是因為我先放了你們的魯索
And you sent them because  I sprung your boy, Russo, in the first place.
我們扯平了  我什麼都不欠你們
We're even. I don't owe you shit.
有個女孩有麻煩  我們幫她一把
There's a girl in trouble. Let's help her out.
- 跟我無關  - 很難說
-Not my problem.  -lt could be.
我們把她送回街上  不知道她會做出什麼事
We put her back on the streets,  there's no telling what she could do.
比起這個，我更怕檢察長
I'm a hell of a lot more afraid  of the U.S. Attorney
而不是什麼妓女
than I am of some hooker.
這是非常便宜的保險投資
This is a very inexpensive insurance policy.
我已經犯過一次法，道格
I already broke the law once, Doug.
我不會挑戰競選財務規範的
There's no fucking way I'm gonna mess  with campaign finance regulations.
我連聽都不想聽
I don't even wanna be hearing this shit.
明天9點半  前日本大使的葬禮
Funeral for the former ambassador of Japan  tomorrow at 9:30,
接著是全委會美國女童軍的
followed by a luncheon with  the National Board of Directors
午餐
for the Girl Scouts of America.
- 總統先生  - 吉姆
-Mr. President.  -Jim.
之後你要接見…
After that, you've got a meet  and greet with the finalist...
我等一下再找你繼續
I'll catch up with you in a minute.
這邊請，先生
This way, sir.
你好
Hi.
Hey.
你來做什麼？
What are you doing here?
議員叫我來的
The Congressman wanted me to come over.
- 為什麼？  - 他想要我來替你競選
-Why?  -He wants me to work for your campaign.
- 副主委  - 法蘭！
-Deputy manager.  -Frank!
他說你現在有些疑慮
He said you're having some doubts.
我正準備告訴他  我決定放棄競選
I was just about to tell him  that I decided not to run.
如果你已經決定  那我也該走了
Okay. If you've made up your mind,  then I should probably get going.
他有跟你說計劃嗎？  說要全盤托出？
Did he tell you about the whole plan?  About coming clean?
他說了
Yeah, he did.
我得考慮到凱文和莎拉
I have Kevin and Sarah to think about.
- 人人都有過去  - 但不是我這種
-Everyone has a past.  -Not like mine.
我有一半的事你不知道  克裏絲汀娜
You don't know  half the things I've done, Christina.
我孩子和他們的朋友會看到  我不能冒這個險
My kids read. Their friends read.  I can't take that chance.
如果你不想參選，就別勉強
Look, if you don't want to run,  then you shouldn't.
我想參選，如果我不想  就不會走到這一步
I do wanna run. I wouldn't have  let it go this far if I didn't want it.
或許這是件好事
Then maybe it's a good thing,
面對你的過去  就算是為了你的孩子
confronting your past, even for your kids.
他們比你想的要堅強得多
They're a lot stronger  than you give them credit for.
如果安德沃和民主黨全委會
Look, if Underwood, if the DNC,
都覺得你能成功，那…
if they all think you can do it, then...
我不在乎他們怎麼想  我只在乎你怎麼想
I don't care what they think.  I care what you think.
你一定會很棒
I think you'd be great.
- 所以她真的想要？  - 我覺得是
-So, she really wants this?  -That's the impression I got.
自尊心呢？我不想伺候女王
What about ego?  I don't need to be dealing with a diva.
她不是女王
She's not a diva,
她是有15年工作經驗  還得過獎的記者
she's an award-winning journalist  with 15 years experience.
你跟我說她對你很糟
You told me she treated you like shit.
我們是有些摩擦
There was some friction.
那你為什麼要挺她？
So why are you going to bat for her?
我們要和頂尖人才合作
Don't we want to work with the best people?
對網站也是好事
Plus, it'd be big for the site.
《先軀報》的資深政治記者？
The Herald's senior political writer?
但她太保守了  只會照本宣科
Sure, but she's so old guard.  Everything's by the book.
沒意思
There's no bite to it.
她說她最近在寫一個人物報導
She told me about a profile she's working on.
- 非常有意思  - 是什麼？
-It's got serious bite.  -What is it?
讓她自己跟你說吧  你該去找她聊聊
She can tell you herself.  You should talk to her.
我有個條件
Here's the deal.
我的孩子不能曝光
My children stay out of the limelight.
不准拍照，不接受採訪
No photo ops, no press.
我們連想都不敢想
We wouldn't dream of it.
好
Okay.
拼了
Let's do this.
汽車旅館
不
No.
你是哪裏人？
Where you from?
林奇堡近郊
Outside of Lynchburg.
維吉尼亞州？
Virginia?
對
Yeah.
- 你父母還住在那裏嗎？  - 不行
-Are your parents still living there?  -No. I can't.
我幫你找個暫時安身的地方  你會自愛嗎？
If I find a place for you to stay for a while,  can I count on you to be smart?
- 什麼地方？  - 很好的地方
-What kind of place?  -A nice place.
一個安全的地方  我們再想永久之計
A safe place until  we can figure out something permanent.
但我要知道  你不會再像這次一樣胡搞
But I need to know  that you won't pull anything like this again.
答應我
Promise me.
我答應你
I promise.
看著我說
Look at me when you say it.
我答應你
I promise you.
你有錢嗎？
How you doing on money?
撐不過明天了
I don't have enough for tomorrow.
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
- 我以為你要我…  - 你說你不做了
-I thought you wanted me to...  -You said you were done with that.
我會和你保持連繫
I'll be in touch.
如果你坦承一些錯誤
If you own up to some of the shenanigans,
再把其他的事隱藏起來  說不定還有機會
sweep the rest under the rug,  you might have a shot.
得隱藏多少事？
How much do we have to sweep under?
這孩子很會掩蓋行蹤
Well, that kid had a talent  for covering his tracks.
我標記了你該坦承的事
I've highlighted all the items  I think you should admit to.
其他的事我絕口不提
The rest I wouldn't mention.
有很多不能說的事
It's a lot not to talk about.
- 我需要你幫我一個忙  - 現在嗎？
-I need your help with something.  -Right now?
- 對  - 重要嗎？
-Yes.  -ls it important?
因為你說這週末我能早點走
Because you told me  I could leave early this weekend
去維吉尼亞州看我的女兒
to go visit my daughter down in Virginia.
你家有間客房吧？
You have a guest room in your house, right?
對，瑪莉從前的房間
Well, it's Mary's old room, but, yes.
我需要你收留一名年輕女孩
I need you to put someone up for a while.  A young woman.
- 什麼？誰？  - 她叫瑞秋
-What? Who?  -Her name is Rachel.
我只能說這麼多
I can't tell you anymore than that.
我不懂，為什麼…
I don't understand. Why do you need...
別問了，南茜  我需要你幫我這個忙
No questions, Nancy.  I just need you to do this for me.
- 事態緊急我才會開口  - 要住多久？
-I wouldn't be asking if it weren't serious.  -Put up for how long?
不知道，一陣子吧
I don't know. It could be a while.
我讓一個陌生人住我家  還不能問問題？
I'm supposed to put up a complete stranger  and not ask any questions?
南茜，拜託  你是我唯一可以相信的人
Nancy, please.  You're the only person I can trust.
有什麼非法的事嗎？
Is something illegal going on?
沒有，她只是碰到麻煩  需要一個住的地方
No. She's just a girl in trouble  who needs a place to stay.
- 我們得低調  - 我能先見她一面嗎？
-We have to be discreet.  -Can I at least meet her first?
我現在就得知道
I need to know now.
應該可以吧
Okay, I guess.
謝謝
Thank you.
沒有陷阱，賴瑞
There's no catch, Larry.
如果數字能維持  你的選區就會有兩千萬
Your district gets over $20 million  if the numbers hold.
大部分資金會被標示為  經濟發展，而不是研究
And most of the money is earmarked  for economic development, not research.
很好，但支持還不夠
That's great, but I need  more than your support.
我需要你當贊助人
I need you to be a sponsor.
太棒了，賴瑞
Fantastic, Larry.
太好了，我會算你一份
Great. I'll put you down.
你也是，拜
You too. Bye.
只剩下克雷本和普萊斯了？
So that just leaves Clayburn and Price?
- 珍妮絲還在觀望  - 我認識羅傑，我來打給他
-With Jennings on the fence.  -And I know Roger. I'll call him.
我週末去找這兩個人
And I'll track down these other two  over the weekend.
今天進展很多，彼得
Really good work today, Peter.
你知道我把皮包放到哪了嗎？
Do you know where I put my purse?
在這裏
It's right here.
這些是你摺的嗎？  不好意思，我不是故意偷看的
Did you make those?  I'm sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
這個？我最近比較愛玩
This?  I've been fooling around with it a little bit.
我能看看嗎？
Can I see?
莎拉在美勞課  學會怎麼摺這種鳥
Sarah learned how to make these birds  in her art class.
然後她教凱文摺  兩個人愛死了
Then she taught it to Kevin,  and they got obsessed,
公寓裏滿地都是紙
and there were little pieces of paper  all over the apartment.
- 要不要拿去送給孩子？  - 不行
-Do you wanna take them for the kids?  -No. I can't.
拿去吧，反正最後也是扔掉
Please.  I'll just throw them out eventually.
謝謝，他們一定會很開心
Thank you. They'll love them.
你該找時間帶孩子來我家  我想認識他們
So you should bring the kids by the house  sometime so I can meet them.
凱文可以和法蘭一起打電動
Kevin and Frank can play the video games.
- 他跟你說了？  - 我承認我有點吃驚
-He told you that?  -I was a little surprised, I have to admit.
如果有人知道他每天回家就…
If anybody knew he came  home every day to...
- 太丟臉了  - 還有比這更糟的秘密
-It's embarrassing.  -There's worse secrets to have.
應該是吧
Yeah, there are, I suppose.
我跟克雷本和普萊斯談過後  週一會打給你
I'll call you Monday  after I talk to Clayburn and Price.
- 好，週末愉快，彼得  - 你也是
-Okay, great. Have a good weekend, Peter.  -You too.
我讓琳達跟副總統談過了
I had Linda talk to the Vice President.
- 他不會插手的  - 十分感謝
-He'll keep his nose out of it.  -I appreciate that.
他是個好人  但現在是競選的敏感時期
He's a good man, but this is a very delicate  moment in the campaign.
- 如果他開始散佈疑慮…  - 他很惹人厭
-He starts spreading doubts, and...  -He's a pain in the ass.
我們都知道  你不用幫他掩飾，法蘭
We all know it.  You don't have to mince words, Frank.
可是我不得不說，長官  副總統說的有點道理
I have to say, sir,  the Vice President has a point.
我無法百分之百支持魯索
I'm not 100% sold on Russo.
真的要用這麼沒經驗的人？
Do we really wanna go  with someone this untested?
- 法蘭？  - 我們在訓練他，長官
-Frank?  -We're grooming him, sir.
- 何時宣佈？  - 下個月
-When do you announce?  -Next month.
- 時間不夠  - 你看中他什麼？
-That's not enough time.  -What do you see in him?
我也在想一樣的問題  他好像沒什麼特別
I was wondering the same thing.  There's not that much to see.
我看中在戒酒的酒癮患者  還有毒癮的經歷
What I see is a recovering alcoholic  with a history of drug abuse.
- 什麼？  - 法蘭，你說什麼？
-What?  -Excuse me, Frank?
但他已經戒一年了
But he's clean now. Has been for a year.
這是個救贖的故事，總統先生
This is a redemption story, Mr. President.
一個充滿希望的年輕人  讓生活重新走上正軌
This is a bright young man  who's put his life back on track.
現在他想讓賓州回到正軌
Now he wants to help  put Pennsylvania back on track.
法蘭，毒品？
Drugs, Frank?
大家都喜歡失敗者，琳達
People love an underdog, Linda,
也喜歡浪子回頭的故事
and people love someone  who stands up after they've fallen.
結合這兩者  就是非常有力的主題
Combine those two,  it's a very powerful narrative.
民調都顯示這會成功
All of our polling  indicates this is gonna work.
你要我們支持  一個有毒癮經歷的人？
You want us to endorse someone  with a history of substance abuse?
讓大家知道他的故事  看選民能不能產生共鳴
Let us get his story out there  and watch it connect with the voters.
我只關心能不能贏，法蘭
All I care about is a win, Frank.
我相信魯索  是贏面最大的人選
And I believe Russo is our best chance.
這不是一場賭局，總統先生  而是深思熟慮的計劃
This is not a Hail Mary, Mr. President,  this is a well-thought-out game plan.
總統先生…
Mr. President...
我知道我有時候  會不照牌理出牌
I realize that I sometimes  think out of the box,
但我上次這麼做時  我們簽署了一項教育提案
but the last time I did,  we signed an education bill.
好吧，我們不會阻攔你
All right. We won't stand in your way.
- 但如果造成反效果，法蘭…  - 我會帶著彼得走每一步
-But if it backfires, Frank...  -I'll guide Peter every step along the way.
我們不會讓你失望的  總統先生
We will not disappoint you, Mr. President.
好
Okay.
謝謝，長官
Thank you, sir.
琳達
Linda.
我沒準備這麼早  讓他們知道這麼多
I didn't plan on telling them  so much so soon,
但如果不說，琳達會影響到他
but if I didn't, Linda would've swayed him.
對抗疑慮最好的方法
There's no better way  to overpower a trickle of doubt
就是赤裸裸的真相
than with a flood of naked truth.
所以教育提案非常重要
This is why the Education Bill  was so important.
在我最需要幫助的時候  替我背書
It bought me influence  precisely when I needed it most.
你酗酒多久了？
How long have you been drinking?
很久了，從小就開始了
A long time. Since I was a kid.
你第一次喝酒是什麼時候？
How old were you  when you had your first drink?
九歲
Nine.
- 九歲？  - 對
-Nine years old?  -Yeah.
我九歲生日時  我爸給了我一杯啤酒
My dad gave me a beer for my ninth birthday.
你什麼時候開始吸毒的？
When did you first start using drugs?
我不會說太多細節
I won't go into too many specifics
只能說我曾經少量吸食過
other than to say I had a few minor brushes
大麻和古柯堿  但最近都沒有再碰了
with marijuana and cocaine  in the past but not recently,
只有過幾次
and only a handful of times.
除了大麻和古柯堿  沒有別的毒品嗎？
No other drugs  besides marijuana and cocaine?
沒有
No.
在什麼樣的情況下？
Under what circumstances?
偶爾的社交場合  我只能說這麼多
Occasional social gatherings.  That's the most I'll say.
擔任公職期間有過嗎？
Ever while you were in public office?
從來沒有  我主要的問題還是酗酒
No. Never. My chief problem was alcohol.
你已經多久沒碰酒精了？
And you've been sober how long now?
一年多
A little over a year.
你為什麼想要戒酒？
And what made you want to get sober?
兩件事
Two things.
我最心愛的孩子
My children, whom I love  more than anything else in the world,
還有我重拾對神的信念
and my renewed faith in God.
喬伊
Zoe.
盧卡斯
Lucas.
我剛好在附近，我想…
I was just in the neighborhood,  and I thought...
我說謊，我剛在轉角的酒吧
No. That's a lie.  I was at the bar around the corner.
就是那個…
The one with the...
我記得那次下班後  我送你回家
And I remembered that time  that I dropped you off after work.
我知道是…
I knew it was...
這附近
This block.
我按了門鈴，然後我等…
And I buzzed, and then I waited...
- 你喝醉了  - 很醉
-You're wasted.  -I'm pretty wasted.
你想不想知道  我心底深處的黑暗秘密？
Do you wanna know a deep, dark secret?
我們已經不是…
Now we don't work together...
同事了
Anymore.
盧卡斯…
Lucas...
我很受寵若驚
I'm really flattered.
但是我現在
But I'm just not in a place
根本沒有時間去想感情的事情
where I'm even  thinking romantically right now.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我…
I...
好
Yeah.
計程車！
Hey, hey!
先生，要繼續開嗎？
You want me to pull up now, sir?
我還留著鑰匙
I still have my key.
我會在廚房  有需要什麼就跟我說
I'll be in the kitchen if you need anything.
謝謝
Thank you.
我買了瓶酒  但我找不到開瓶器
Hey, I got us wine,  but I can't find a corkscrew anywhere.
給我吧
Give it to me.
我需要一支筆
I need a pen.
- 總統給你的那支？  - 可以
-The pen the President gave you?  -That'll work.
跟史柯斯基小姐談過了嗎？
Did you talk to Ms. Skorsky?
有，她說很困難
I did. She said it was intense.
卡莉應該會找她過來  《頭條報導》
I think Carly's  gonna offer her a job at Slugline.
- 是你促成的嗎？  - 珍妮有興趣
-Was that your doing?  -Janine expressed interest.
我就順水推舟
I took the next step.
做得好  永遠要讓別人欠你人情
Well done. Always good to be owed favors.
我剛在想  你考慮過我年齡的事嗎？
I was wondering.  Do you ever think about my age?
沒有，我的年齡讓你不安？
No. Does my age bother you?
你一定還有比我年輕的情人
You must have other lovers,  men that are younger than me.
- 沒有  - 我不會介意
-No.  -Not that I would mind.
反正我是有婦之夫
I am married, after all.
我沒有時間給其他情人
I don't have time for other lovers.
可惡
Shit.
變味了，給我
It's turned. Give me that.
直接踩死不就好了
You could've just stepped on it.
我請管理員幫我放殺蟲劑
I have asked the super  to get an exterminator in here,
但他不肯
and he won't do it.
所以我只要看到蟑螂  或蜘蛛之類的
So any time I see a cockroach,  or a spider, or whatever,
就會試著抓起來  然後放到他門口
I try and trap it,  and then I leave it by his door.
你真該跟你爸媽借點錢
You really ought to get your parents  to let you borrow some money.
就不用住在第三世界了
Then you wouldn't have to live  in the third world.
我不會跟他們要錢的
I would never take money from them.
因為他們沒有錢  還是你不想要？
Because they don't have it,  or because you don't want it?
因為我不想要
Because I don't want it.
今天是父親節
It's Father's Day, you know.
是嗎？
It is?
你應該打給你爸爸
You should call your father.
我明天再打
I'll call him tomorrow.
明天你就變成  忘了父親節的女兒
Tomorrow you'll be the daughter  that forgot Father's Day
而不是記得的女兒
instead of the one who remembered.
去吧，打給他
Go ahead. Call him.
爸，不好意思這麼晚打給你
Hey, Dad. Sorry it's so late.
因為我上次打給她的時候  你不在家
'Cause you weren't home  the last time I called her.
我跟她之間  會互相透露的事情非常少
There's so little she'll ever reveal to me  or I to her.
我敢說她爸爸知道的更少
I bet her father knows even less.
她現在聲音一定高了八度
I'm sure she's speaking  half an octave higher.
就像她16歲時的聲音一樣
Same voice she had when she was 16.
跟他說她的新工作  她有多想他
Telling him all about her new job,  how much she misses him,
抱歉她忘了寄卡片
and sorry she didn't send a card.
什麼都會說，除了真相
Telling him everything but the truth.
就像她不會告訴我  樓下的年輕男生是誰
Just like she wouldn't tell me  about that young man downstairs.
我打了啊
I'm calling now, all right?
你會讓我心情不好
You're gonna make me feel bad about it.
這是最棒的發展
It was the best thing that could've happened.
我在那裏格格不入
I didn't fit in there.
我聽過更糟的形容詞，爸
I've been called worse, Dad.
秘密是有價值的
There's a value in having secrets.
像我、克萊兒  還有喬伊這樣的生物
Creatures like myself, like Claire, like Zoe,
如果沒有秘密  我們就不是自己了
we wouldn't be ourselves without them.
但另一方面，彼得魯索  被自己的秘密困住
But Peter Russo, on the other hand,  he's trapped by his secrets.
我正試著給他一個機會
What I'm trying to do  is give him the opportunity
重獲自由
to set himself free.
我不知道
I don't know.
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
我們終究只是  自己選擇透露出來的表象
After all, we are nothing  more or less than what we choose to reveal.
我在克萊兒和喬伊面前  不是同一個人
What I am to Claire is not what I am to Zoe,
就像喬伊  在我和她爸爸面前也不一樣
just as Zoe is not to me  what she is to her father.
大概感恩節吧
Probably Thanksgiving.
因為在那之前我應該回不去
'Cause I don't think I can  make it back before then.
好，我盡量
Okay. I'll try.
我說了，我盡量
I said I'll try.
聖誕節？
For Christmas?
不行
No.
沒有，我現在沒有對象
No. I'm not seeing anyone right now.
我還不想
I don't feel like it.
因為我沒興趣
Because I'm not interested in that.
我會告訴你的，爸
I would tell you, Dad.
好
Yeah.
Okay.
別擔心我，我很好
Don't be worried about me. I'm fine.
好
Yeah.
爸，我…
Dad, I'm in...
我現在過得很好
I'm in a really great place right now.
我盡量
I'm gonna try.
我會盡量回去，好嗎？
I'm gonna try to come, okay?
父親節快樂
Happy Father's Day.
你不祝我父親節快樂嗎？
Aren't you gonna  wish me a happy Father's Day?
你又沒小孩
You don't have any children.
是嗎？
Don't l?